<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blogs on Solitarian</title>
    <link>https://solitarian.ca/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blogs on Solitarian</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 30 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://solitarian.ca/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Running</title>
      <link>https://solitarian.ca/blog/running/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://solitarian.ca/blog/running/</guid>
      <description>After my last post about my yearly theme I thought I’d write some posts about what I actually do to take care of myself in 2021. One of the biggest changes I’ve made started prior to 2021 that will be with me for years to come is running. I’m not a particularly fast runner, but I am proud of the progression I’ve made since I started.
A while back I was at a low point in my life where I was mentally depleted and physically unhealthy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yearly Theme</title>
      <link>https://solitarian.ca/blog/yearly-theme/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://solitarian.ca/blog/yearly-theme/</guid>
      <description>As a regular listener to the Cortex podcast on Relay FM I’ve become interested in their discussions on yearly themes every year. This year I’ve decided to set one for myself.
As I regularly fail New Years resolutions, the idea of setting a theme for the year seemed like a better way to bring about some positive change. There are no rules to the yearly themes. CGP Grey has a good video on the topic that explains it clearly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My First Post</title>
      <link>https://solitarian.ca/blog/first-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://solitarian.ca/blog/first-post/</guid>
      <description>My thoughts about coming back to writing started with an article I read by Ana Rodrigues last month. Long ago I was blogging and sharing links on my own domain before there was Twitter and Facebook. I ran the server off my home computer, that I built myself, and wrote the HTML on a document that I uploaded with FTP. Back then I experimented with Linux, FreeBSD and different content management systems.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
